It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
Good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
Positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry!
He's a family guy!
Ah, the last small sip of beer,
always terrible.
Hey, I'll catch you guys later,
I'm heading out.
Leaving early on a Saturday?
I think someone has a lady friend, huh?
-Huh?
-Ow! My dormant tricep!
There's no girl. I, I...
I just like watching the classic SNL
that comes on before the new SNL.
And tonight, the classic SNL is...
Deion Sanders with musical guest
Deion Sanders? No, that can't be right.
Sadly, it is right.
He sang songs from his
album, Prime Time.
Come on, Quagmire,
tell us who the girl is.
You're the only one of us who can date.
We live bi-curiously through you.
Yeah. That's our penis.
Sorry, guys, but this one's top secret.
Forgot that a homeless guy sits out front.
He's very yelly tonight.
Huh, it's not like Quagmire to hold
out on us.
There must be a reason.
Yeah, we got ourselves quite a mystery.
Could even be an episode of
Murder She Wrote
with Angela Lansbury and Paul McCartney.
Well, she's dead.
She sure is, Paul.
You're Paul. I'm Angela.
And one of us either looks like
an old woman or an old man.
That's the real mystery.
Is James Corden nice?
Not really, no.
Okay, Brian, I'll crack a window
so you can wait in the car.
Ha! You can't come in 'cause you're
a freakin' dog!
Come on, you can't leave me here.
It's inhumane!
Sorry, those are the rules.
They only let in humans and squirrels.
-What?
-I'm just kidding.
Bye, babe.
Alright, Stewie, hold my hand while
I get our reusable bags from the trunk.
Calm down.
Where am I gonna run? The market?
It's not like it's mango season.
The mango bell?
Attention shoppers, mangos will be ripe
for the next two-and-a-half minutes.
I've gotta get in there!
Wow, that was close.
I've never killed someone
outside the hospital.
Oh my God, Stewie!
You could have been run over!
Sorry, I was texting while driving.
Unfortunately, your husband derd.
Whoops, oh no, I meant...
Ah, she haha'd it.
Yeah, she's a good sport.
Okay, Quagmire said he can't go to
the Clam tonight,
so I bet he's meeting that
mystery woman again.
Yep, now, I know you fellas haven't been
on a stakeout before,
but I've been on a ton of them.
So, I just want to mentally prepare
you for how long these things...
Oop, there he is.
Alright, let's tail him.
And this high-speed adventure calls for
a classic action movie theme!
I'm romancing the stone
What is this?
It's Eddy Grant's theme to
Romancing the Stone.
This is stupid.
I'm finding another song.
They do what they want to do,
say what they want
What the hell is this?
"Addams Groove" by MC Hammer.
It's the theme song to
The Addams Family movie.
It went to number four in Ireland.
And this is better?
Your guy just keeps saying the name
of the movie!
I'm turning mine up.
Then I'm turning mine up!
Will you guys please turn off your
terrible theme songs?
Sorry, Joe.
Guys, I think Quagmire's getting away.
Yeah, look, Joe. He's making a right.
Don't worry, I'm on it.
I'm running over stuff at
The Forum this Sunday.
You'll pay for the whole seat,
but you'll only need the edge.
Hey, Lois. I'm taking Stewie to the park.
Come on, Bri, I need a post that
will make Lance think I'm outdoorsy.
Hold on, before you go, I got something.
Yes! You're gettin' leashed!
Ah, I'm going to film my reaction
in slow-mo.
It's for Stewie.
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?
After that close call at the store,
I want to make sure he cannot
run away again.
So, I bought this.
It's a child harness.
That's not a harness, it's a leash!
A harness is something Rupert and I use
on my birthday.
I thought you two also use a leash.
Well, I guess someone's been listening
at the door.
No, you texted me.
Well, either way, I demand this be taken
off at once!
Children don't belong in leashes.
Just like Bill Burr doesn't belong
in The Mandalorian.
I've located the child.
He's on an Empire ship.
I'll assemble a strike team.
I'll jam the ship's radar.
And I'm gonna go whiz in a Gatorade bottle
'cause I don't trust space toilets.
Uh, which part of space are
you from again?
South space!
Quagmire, come on, we tee off in an hour.
Don't worry, I'll register us online
to save time.
Name? Joe Swanson.
Handicap? Yes.
Quagmire, let's go!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Ooh, he must be with the mystery girl.
-I bet she's married.
-Or famous.
Oh, my God!
Quagmire and the Librarian?
Wow! At the library, I guess Quagmire's
been checking out more than just books.
Come on, don't encourage him.
I can't believe it.
Yeah. And she's got BB-8 underwear.
Lois said they don't make those!
Guys, I'd appreciate if you'd leave now.
Yeah, sure, let me just tie my shoe.
Peter, is that R2-D2 underwear?
Yeah, they're old and stupid.
You and the Librarian.
I don't get it.
Yeah, did, like, a bully dare you
to invite her to prom
and then it turned into something more?
Or, your boss is a family man,
and you're just pretending to date her
to get the big promotion?
No, there's no '90s movie
premise involved!
See, this is why I didn't want to tell you
guys about her.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
Then, help us understand, Glenn.
Show us your world.
Dammit Peter, you just had chicken wings!
I just like her, okay.
She's nice, she's smart.
And when you ask her where she wants
to eat dinner,
she always has a clear, confident answer.
-No way!
-You lie!
It's true! And it's nice to date someone
where I can relax and be myself.
I don't even have to hide my
moderate-to-severe plaque psoriasis.
You have plaque psoriasis?
Well, I did before Skyrizi.
I can't see me lovin' nobody but you
For all my life
Skyrizi may cause general douchery,
like spinning at weddings and sky hooking
paper into trash cans.
Thanks, Skyrizi!
Now my elbows are ugly for the same reason
as everybody else.
And that's not even the best
thing about her.
Believe it or not, fellas,
she's the best I've ever had in bed.
The Librarian?
Yeah, she spent the last 30 years
sitting at a reference desk,
reading back issues
of Cosmopolitan Magazine.
That means she's read over four million
tips on how to please her lover.
You know, you guys would like her
if you'd just give her a chance.
I don't know. Us?
Hang out with a librarian?
Yeah, I don't think we're a match.
Like William Wallace and the guy
who wouldn't wear face paint.
They may take our lives,
but they will never take our...
Hey, where's your face paint?
I can no wear it.
I have the plaque psoriasis.
Or at least, I did before Skyrizi.
I can't see me lovin' nobody but you
Now this is freedom!
Ugh, this thing is so humiliating.
Ah, it's not a big deal.
I'm sure no one will even notice.
Oh, crap! It's Jake from my gym,
boxing an MMA mannequin.
Stewie?
Uh, hey, Jake. Just, uh, doing
some resistance training.
Heard about it on Rogan.
Nice. Love Rogan.
Yes, he's for the vanguard
of independent thinkers
who also have seven hours a day to listen
to a shaved ape.
Okay, Brian, I think I covered
nicely there.
I'm gonna go play.
Oh! What the hell?
Uh, looks like we got our leashes tangled.
Sorry about that. My little guy doesn't
always look where he's going.
Uh, Brian, I think he's trying
to establish dominance.
Ah, he's just being friendly.
Sir, sir?
You cannot sniff back there.
Alright, that's it.
Two can play at this game, tough guy.
Wow, you're six.
And from Denver?
Huh, there's a lot of
information in butts.
I get it now.
I'm so excited to be here with you guys!
Okay, good start, shows energy.
Peter, this isn't a tryout.
Sorry. So, Elle, uh...
Hey, what are your arm tattoos?
Oh, those are my three babies that never
came to term.
Oh, wow. Uh...
Uh, yeah, maybe, maybe uh...
maybe you just long sleeve it.
Or don't say it.
Yeah, sleeve it or don't say it.
Oh, I stopped sleeving when
I started Skyrizi.
Enough with Skyrizi!
Do Taco Bell! At least they're a sponsor!
So, uh, anyway, on the way here,
Elle was saying how much she likes beer.
No, I didn't. I said the library
masturbator ruined another atlas.
Okay, look. This ain't working.
Elle, we're regular guys.
You're a librarian, all right?
I don't know the first
thing about libraries,
except that the atlases are sexy.
Hell, I only even go to the library for
the puppet show 'cause I like King Puppet.
You mean this puppet?
Quagmire, I love her.
You hit it out of the park.
Hey, do you know the guy who
does Prince Puppet?
Yes, but the prince is a little shy.
Oh my God, how is this happening?
I'm just Peter Griffin!
Well, Peter may like you.
But good luck winning over the Joe.
Aren't you the cop who hid in the library
when he heard "shots fired"?
Never mind, you won the Joe.
I also believe
in essential oils.
Would anyone like eucalyptus
for their nose?
No, that's stupid.
Ooh!
That's nice.
I can see why women make this crap
their whole personality.
Ah, this is great.
I'm so glad you guys are getting along.
We sure are.
And I love this eucalyptus.
I feel like Koala Peter.
Hey Mum, I'm gonna pick some of
these Tasmanian berries.
Oi Crikey! Me peepers!
I'm meaner than you think.
Connor, no! No!
All right, you can sniff the hydrant.
Aidan, no jumping!
I said no jumping!
Ah, never make your hobby your job.
Ooh, Brian, they have a movie
with animals singing!
Pass. Hi, do you have anything with any
of the girls from Euphoria?
Oh, come on!
Miley Cyrus plays a sassy giraffe!
Demi Lovato also plays a sassy giraffe!
And Halsey plays...
Oh, you know,
I think it's a movie about giraffes.
Listen, if you're looking to be a creep,
all I can offer you is Jennifer Connelly
in Hot Widow.
Yeah, that works.
How dark does the theater get?
Sir, movie theaters are
a failing business,
you can do whatever you want.
No! Animals singing!
Stewie, enough!
We're not seeing animals singing!
Ow! Okay, we'll...
We'll see yours instead.
Wow!
After all this time of putting up with
your snide comments
and domineering attitude,
I'm finally in control.
All right, let's go see my movie!
Yes, Brian.
Whatever you want.
Too late. They just turned this place
into pickleball courts.
What?
Movie theaters!
What a debacle!
Thanks for bringing Elle the other night.
She's really something.
She sure is.
I don't get my shirt dry-cleaned for
just any date.
This weekend, I'm asking her to make
our relationship official.
Why don't you just ask her now,
when she gets done kissing that other guy?
What?
Elle, what are you doing?
Glenn.
Hi.
Well, the top stars of puppetry
are often unfaithful.
You knew the risks.
God, this is so humiliating.
Captain Quagmire?
Nestor? The guy with batons who directs
my plane to the gate?
Oh, God! This is...
This is even more humiliating!
Actually, I'm called a "marshaller."
Yeah, I don't think that's a real term,
but I can't believe this.
Thank God other pilots don't
hang out here.
Glenn Quagmire and the marshaller?
Okay, I guess that is a term.
Oh, Glenn.
I'm sorry to have to tell you like this,
but I just, I don't think you and I
are working out.
What? Why?
We get along great!
I know.
The problem is in bed.
You've just, you've never given
me an orgasm.
What?
Calling all cars,
we have a man ripped to pieces
at 42 Maple.
Heartbroken, guts pulled right out.
Suspect is a saucy librarian.
A strangler got away 'cause I was goofin'
on the radio.
Hey, guys.
Hey, you hear about Glenn Quagmire?
Can't pleasure a woman.
Peter, that's me!
Oh, sorry, I thought I was somewhere else.
Anyway, we haven't told anyone.
How ya doin', buddy?
Well, you know, it was a shock at first,
but I'm starting to adjust.
I've gotten really into running ten Ks,
I garden now,
and I even bought season tickets
for the Orioles,
since that's what guys who can't
satisfy women do.
-What's that?
-My new car.
I traded in my convertible for
a Toyota Yaris.
Sign here that you're incapable of
satisfying a woman.
Great, and I'm so sorry,
you now own a Yaris.
-I also got a nice text from Josh Charles.
-What?
When a guy can't please a woman,
he gets a text from Josh Charles.
He's kind of the leader of our community.
Okay, well, I guess things aren't
so bad then.
Of course they are!
I hate my life now!
I can't even be a pilot anymore because
the passengers don't respect me.
Bye now. Thanks for flying.
Ma'am, can I help you get off?
Hmm! Not from what I hear.
I was also on that flight.
And then I got a cease and desist order
from the people who license
the word "giggity."
-What?
-It's a standard franchise agreement,
but apparently it can only be used by men
who can satisfy their partners.
Hey, guys. I'm just gonna trim
this overgrown bush.
Go... Go...
Oh God, what am I gonna do?
Thanks, Josh.
Guys, we have to do something.
Yeah, we gotta help him get his mojo back.
Come on, Quagmire, let's get you up.
Yeah, I hate seeing you like this.
And I wanna know who the hell has
"giggity" right now.
Giggity!
You know what?
Good for the giggity people.
Embracing change.
Uh, Stewie, do I need to take
out the leash?
Sorry, Bri.
So, listen, I have to change my flight and
I need you to wait on hold for me.
Oh, come on! That'll take forever!
This is Celia, how may I help you?
Oh, thank God. My name is Brian Griffin.
I'm calling about Flight 432 to Chicago.
Tell her I want a flight with zero
male flight attendants.
That's what I'm calling for?
And, and I want to sit next to
a half-Asian chick.
How would they even know that?
I heard your requests.
You are now on flight 376.
And sitting next to Grace Thompson-Woo.
-Really?
-Yes.
We do this all the time for James Franco.
All right! Now call Ticketmaster.
You've reached Ticketmaster.
Good luck, douchebag.
Ticketmaster, what a debacle!
Alright, Quagmire, we're going to tell you
everything we know about lovemaking
to help you excite women again.
Yeah, and everything I know,
I learned from amateur porn.
Do you have a Jacksonville Jaguars hat
you can put on backwards?
I don't think this is helpful, Peter.
I want to have real sex.
Oh, well, then the key is to eat
a giant steak,
and then fall asleep on top of Lois.
She loves that.
Or maybe try some scented body butter.
I rub some on before relations with Donna.
By the end of the night, she's like
Yosemite Sam with two guns.
She says I have the rootin'est-tootin'est,
girthiest-sturdiest,
most positively elephantiest
jackhammer in all the West.
Okay.
Or hey, maybe you're just not
a sex guy anymore?
Maybe you date the girls, but another
fella steps in for, uh, the sex.
That's what Bon and I do.
This poor sap's upstairs nailing my wife,
meanwhile I'm in the basement,
knocking out Frasier's left and right.
Guys, this has been
spectacularly unhelpful.
Well, what do you want us to do?
You're the sex guy in the group.
Not anymore I'm not.
Thanks for trying, but...
Let's be honest, I'm old.
I'm washed up.
My days of pleasing women are behind me.
You guys can let yourselves out.
I think I'm gonna take a nap.
Who else but Quagmire?
What'd you say to me?
You heard me. Who else could hit on
my wife for 20 years?
Quagmire.
Who else could sleep with my first wife?
So, don't you give me this crap
that you're old and washed up.
You'll never be. And you know why?
'Cause who else but Quagmire?
I'll tell you who else, no one!
I'm gonna go out there, get my mojo back,
and then I'm giving Elle the time
of her life!
The Toyota Yaris, what a debacle!
Ah, it's a great day for a walk.
Uh, yeah, yeah. When the wind made that
fence rattle, you...
-You did a good job barking at it.
-Thank you.
It was a crisis and I feel
like I took charge.
Hey, what do you say we take another lap
around the block?
Oh, I don't know. I'm really tired now,
and my diaper lost contain.
Come on, we're taking another lap.
Please! Rupert and I ate at
a cantina last night.
I don't care, Stewie!
I have the leash, so I'm in control!
Okay, well, two dogs are
disappointed in me.
And they should be.
Look at me.
I've become a power-hungry,
inhumane dog owner that I despise.
I'm sorry, Stewie.
I never should have treated you like this.
You don't need a leash.
You need to be free.
Really?
That's right, pal.
Ooh! The ice cream truck!
Ow! Did you see the driver?
It was Caitlyn Jenner again.
God! How is Caitlyn Jenner still
allowed to drive?
That was practically manslaughter!
More like they/them slaughter.
You know what? I don't think
we're qualified to talk about this.
Glenn?
Hello, gorgeous!
These are for you.
I took your criticism to heart,
and I'm here to let you know,
I've upped my game!
I have more stamina, more flexibility,
and you know that trick where someone ties
a knot with a cherry stem?
Dammit, ow.
That was much more painful than
I thought it'd be.
Oh, I don't know, Glenn.
Are you sure you can handle me?
Better question.
Can you handle me?
All right, let's load him in!
What happened?
O.I.A.
Orgasm Induced Aneurysm.
Poor guy slept with someone out
of his league.
I gotta say, his elbows look perfect.
Thanks, Skyrizi.
Well, Elle may not have worked out,
but a lot of women still enjoy my company.
I guess Elle was just too much
woman for me.
And perhaps anyone.
Hi, I'm John Mayer.
I put my skinny arms in a t-shirt today
to let you know that every year,
over a 1000 men die from
an Orgasm Induced Aneurysm, or O.I.A.
Every guy wants sex to be mind-blowing
but not like this.
So, please, donate to stop O.I.A. today,
and help us make every man's body
a wonderland.
Should I play the song now?
No, the guy was from Boston,
so we're gonna do that screaming,
shanty rock that makes Bruins fans
punch each other in the face.